# Donna Griffith

45170 Kincora Drive Apt. 328 Sterling, VA 20166 | 540-216-1681 | loomisdl@amazon.com

#### **Summary**

Natural leader and customer obsessed professional with 5 years of Amazon experience as a Global Executive Relations Specialist, Team Manager and Customer Service Associate. Have worked in multiple spaces such as Amazon Flex Escalations, Retail, Amazon Fresh, Prime Now, GSF3, Shipping and Delivery Support (SDS), and Concession Abuse Prevention (CAP). Looking for the opportunity to further advocate for our customers and drivers.

### **Skills & Abilities**

- · Responding to inquiries on behalf of corporate executives including Amazon CEOs, VPs, and other Senior Leaders
- · Strong verbal, written communication and presentation skills
- · Communicating effectively with other departments and stakeholders
- · Passion for deep dive projects and process improvement
- · Excellent time management and organizational skills
- · High attention to detail and ability to take initiative to resolve issues
- · Ability to work independently and multitask in a fast-paced, quickly changing environment

### **Experience**

#### SDS EDR Specialist | AMAZON | OCTOBER 2021 - PRESENT

- · Converted to permanent role on May 29, 2022
- · Overall Quality Score in the last six months is 96%
- $\cdot$  Overall Quality Score since conversion is 99%
- · SDS EXR SME Program Supporting IN SDS EDR Specialists
- · Resolve complex driver issues that have been escalated to the Amazon CEO
- · Advocate for Amazon Flex drivers in High Severity situations
- · Deep dive and analyze the root cause of driver pain points

### SDS GSF3 TEAM MGR [A] | AMAZON | MAY 2021 - AUGUST 2021

- · Exceeded Q2 Metric goals
- · Performed a minimum of 50 Quality Audits per week
- · Performed weekly metric deep dives with Red hawk, Alchemy, and Excel Pivot Tables

### NALMTOC AND SDS CAP TEAM MGR [A] | AMAZON | APRIL 2020 - FEBRUARY 2021

- · Performed a minimum of 50 Quality Audits per week
- · Maintained an average Leadership Behavior Connections score of 4.9 over the last 6 months
- · Performed weekly metric deep dives with Red hawk, Alchemy, and Excel Pivot Tables

## CUSTOMER SERVICE ASSOCIATE | AMAZON | OCTOBER 2017 - MAY 2021

- · Transitioned through multiple departments Retail, Amazon Fresh, GSF3, SDS
- · Effectively handled contacts through phone, chat, and email
- · Selected by mangers and peers as a Subject Matter Expert in GSF3

#### **Education**

VIOLIN/VIOLA PERFORMANCE | 1997 - 2001 | SHENANDOAH CONSERVATORY